Guide to the David A. Clarke papers, 1974-1997 MS2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Part 1 (donated 1990), 1976-1990; Series 1; 82 Linear Feet
  - Subject files, 1976-1990; Series 1 Subseries 1
    - Historic Mt. Pleasant,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Hobart Place Block Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Julius Hobson Plaza Condominium Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Hoffman,Michael D., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Hogan and Hartson, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Holman,Moses Carl, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Holy Temple Church of Christ,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Home Rule Study, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Home Rule 10-Year Anniversary, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Home and School Institute,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Home Court, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Homeless Advisory Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Homeless Coordinating Committee of Jr. League of Washington, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Homeless Issues (1 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Homeless Issues (2 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Homeless Issues (3 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Homeless Issues (4 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Homeless Issues (5 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Homeless Issues (6 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Homeless Issues (7 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Homeless Issues (8 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Homeless Issues (9 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Homeless Issues (10 of 10), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Homestead, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Hooper,Micheal (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Hooper,Micheal (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Hope Village, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Horizon House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Horning Brothers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - The Hospital for Sick Children, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Hospital Workers Union "SEIO" 722, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Hot Pepper, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Hotel Association of D.C. (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Hotel Association of D.C. (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Employees Local 25, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Employees Local 25, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Hotel Washington, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Hotels, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - House of Delegates, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - House of the Imagene, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - House of Laureze, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - House of Mercy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - House of Prayer, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - House of Representatives, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - House of Ruth, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Housing (1 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Housing (2 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Housing (3 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Housing (4 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Housing (5 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Housing Action Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Housing Code Violations (1 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Housing Code Violations (2 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Housing Code Violations (3 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Housing Code Violations (4 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Housing Code Violations (5 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Housing Code Violations (6 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Housing Counseling Services,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Housing and Economic Development Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Housing for the Elderly (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Housing for the Elderly (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Housing Now, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Housing Production Trust Fund, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Howard Gardens, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Howard Gateway/Shaw Sterring Committee (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Howard Gateway/Shaw Sterring Committee (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Howard Theatre Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Howard University (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Howard University (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Howard University Alumni Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Howard University Alumni Club of D.C.,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Howard University Cancer Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Howard University The Center for Academic Reinforcement, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Howard University Center for Sickle-Cell Disease, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Howard University College of Pharmacy and Pharmacal Sciences, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Howard University Connection Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Howard University Credit Union, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Howard University Department of Alumni Affairs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Howard University Division of Student Affairs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Howard University Hospital (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Howard University Hospital (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Howard University Law Alumni Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Howard University Law School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Howard University Salute to Blacks in Business, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Howard University School of Business and Public Administration, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Howard University School of Communications, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Howard University School of Divinity, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Howard University School of Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Howard University School of Medicine, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Howard University Student Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Howard University Women's Club,D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Langston Hughes Democratic Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Hughes Memorial United Methodist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Human Resources Institute, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Human Resources Research Organization Tec. (HumRROTec), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Human Rights Day, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Human Rights Internet (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Human Rights Internet (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - The Humanist, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Hunger Action, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Hunton and Williams, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Hurt Home Committee (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Hurt Home Committee (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - E.F. Hutton,Co., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Hyatt Regency Washington on Capitol Hill, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Ibero-American Chamber of Commerce, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - IBM, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Ideamatics, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Illinois, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Immigration, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Imperial Embassy of Iran, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Imperial Tenants Association (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Imperial Tenants Association (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Inaugural Committee of 1987, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Income Taxes, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Incoming, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Independence Federal Savings Bank, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Independence Federal Savings Bank/Student Loan Application, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Independent Funeral Directors Association of Washington,D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Independent Living for the Handicapped,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - India (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - India (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Indices (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Indices (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Indigent Care Public Policy Forum, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Indochinese Community Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - In-Ernest Productions, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Infant Mortality, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Information Center for Handicapped Individuals,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Information Center for Protection,and Advocacy Center for Handicapped Individuals Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Initiative 17, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Inner Voices, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Institute for Afro-American Scholarship, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Institute for Afro-Latin American Studies, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Institute for Gifted and Talented, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Institute for Labor/Management, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Institute for Local Self-Reliance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Institute of International Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Mental Hygiene, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Institute for Neighborhood Reinvestment and Minority Business Research, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Institute for Policy Studies, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Institute for Rational Public Policy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Institute of Real Estate Management, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Institute for Strategic Management, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Institute for Urban Living, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Inter-City Trash Service,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Intercollegiate Pentecostal Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Interfaith Conference of Metropolitan Washington,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - International Affairs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - International Association for Black Professional Fire Fighters, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - International Association of Chief of Police, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - International Brotherhood of Police Officers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - International Cultural and Trade Center (1 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - International Cultural and Trade Center (2 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - International Cultural and Trade Center (3 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - International Cultural and Trade Center (4 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - International Cultural and Trade Center (5 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - International Cultural and Trade Center (6 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - International Developers Inc. (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - International Developers Inc. (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - International Franchise Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - International Investment Project, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - International Leadership Roundtable, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - International Monetary Fund, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - International Monetary Fund Visitors' Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - International Order of Odd Fellows, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - International Peace Museum in D.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - International Sister City Program, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - International Task Force of the League of Cities, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - International Training in Communication, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - International Training and Communications Progressive Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - International Village (1 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - International Village (2 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - International Village (3 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - International Village (4 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - International Village (5 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - International Village (6 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - International Village (7 of 7), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - International Women's Convention of the Church of God in Christ, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Interstate Commission on the Potomac River Basin, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Invitation List (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Invitation List (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Invitation List (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Invitation to the White House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Invitational AmateurBoxing Tournament, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Iona House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Irish National Caucus - MacBride Principles, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Irish Republican Club of North America, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Islamic Universal Cultural Organization, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Isle of Patmos Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Israel Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Israel Metropolitan Methodist Episcopal Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Italian Festival,5th Annual, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Jack and Jill of America,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Jesse Jackson Campaign, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Jesse Jackson Campaign Press Conference, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Michael Jackson Concert Tickets, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Samuel Jackson Plaza, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Jackson School Art Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - J.A.M., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Jameson's Liquor,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Jazz Karma Records, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Jeep Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Jeffery Gardens Tenant Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Jefferson House Unit Owners Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Jefferson Street Civic Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Jelleff Advisory Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - The Jenco Group, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Jennifers,Joseph, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Jerusalem Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Jerusalem Passion Play, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Jesus of Nazareth Prison Ministry, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Jesus-Washington Area Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Jewel Fair, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Jewels of Ann Private School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Jewish National Fund, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Jewish Social Service Agency, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Genevieve Johnson, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Johnson,Lemon,and Co., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Join Us In Prayer?, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Jones Memorial United Methodist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Joy of Motion Dance Center,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Joyner Associates, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Jubilee Housing Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Judicial Appointment Authority Legislation (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Judicial Appointment Authority Legislation (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Judicial Nomination Commission, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Judicial System Autonomy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Judiciary House Resident Council Organization, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Julia West Hamilton League, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Julian Travel Associate, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - July 4th Family Celebration, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Junior Achievement of Metropolitan Washington,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Junior Citizen's Corp, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Junior Fire Marshals, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Jury Reform (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Jury Reform (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Justice for Janitors Organizing Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Justice System Board (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Justice System Board (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Justice,Unity,Generosity,and Service (JUGS), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Juvenile Justice Advisory Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - K/B Theatres, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - K and M Ventures, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - The Kaempfer Company, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Kalorama Cafe, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Kalorama Citizens Association (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Kalorama Citizens Association (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Kalorama Parents Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - 1745 Kalorama Road,N.W., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Kamber Group, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Kaohsiung City Government- Republic of China, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Kappa Alpha Psi Fraternity, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Kass and Skalet,P.C., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Samuel Kelsey Apartments, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Keneshaw Apartments (1 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Keneshaw Apartments (2 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Keneshaw Apartments (3 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Keneshaw Apartments (4 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Keneshaw Apartments (5 of 5), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Kenilworth/Parkside Resident Management Corp., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Kennedy Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Kennedy Institute Community, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Robert F. Kennedy Memorial Human Rights Awards, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Kennedys-King Dinner, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Kenyon Street Block Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 22)